<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Tom Rose, Philadelphia Freelance WordPress Developer</title>
    <link>https://tomrose.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Tom Rose, Philadelphia Freelance WordPress Developer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tomrose.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tomrose.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomrose.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there. I&#39;m Tom Rose, a freelance WordPress developer with over 20 years experience building websites with HTML, CSS and JavaScript. I have a strong passion for web standards, clean code and keeping things simple. I love building websites that display content clearly, load fast and are easy to navigate.
I mainly work out of my home office in West Philadelphia, but I’m always excited to join teams onsite when possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://tomrose.dev/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomrose.dev/contact/</guid>
      <description>Have a project you&#39;d like to discuss? I&#39;d love to set up a time to talk. Please fill out the form below and I&#39;ll get back to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curalate</title>
      <link>https://tomrose.dev/projects/curalate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomrose.dev/projects/curalate/</guid>
      <description>Curalate is social commerce platform that helps brands connect with users and buyers. I worked with the in-house design and marketing teams (often onsite at their Philadelphia headquarters) to build a custom, responsive WordPress theme to promote their platform. The project included development of a blog with searchable taxonomies, a sortable partnerships section, various demo form landing pages and a developers guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indicative</title>
      <link>https://tomrose.dev/projects/indicative/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomrose.dev/projects/indicative/</guid>
      <description>Indicative is a behavioral analytics platform based in New York City. I worked with a talented freelance designer to build a custom WordPress theme for their main marketing website. The theme includes custom components built with the amazing Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) plugin. With ACF, editors in the Indicative office can easily add pricing info, product details, blog posts and the like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suzanne Lovell</title>
      <link>https://tomrose.dev/projects/lovell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomrose.dev/projects/lovell/</guid>
      <description>Suzanne Lovell is a award-winning architect and interior designer based in Chicago. I again collaborated with another amazing designer to build a component system that in-house editors could use to build blog posts, case studies and general content pages. Each page on the site is generated from responsive components that can be re-ordered and dragged/dropped as needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United World Mission</title>
      <link>https://tomrose.dev/projects/uwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomrose.dev/projects/uwm/</guid>
      <description>United World Mission equips leaders and establishes churches around the world. Working with Rethink Creative, a design shop based in New Jersey, I built a framework that allows users to search for opportunities and donate money to workers and projects. These pages utilize JavaScript and WordPress&amp;rsquo; amazing taxonomy API to return data quickly and accurately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uwishunu</title>
      <link>https://tomrose.dev/projects/uwishunu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomrose.dev/projects/uwishunu/</guid>
      <description>Collaborating with the mighty WebDevStudios, I took the role of lead designer on the redesign of Uwishunu, a popular events website in Philadelphia. This project involved several onsite meetings at the clients&amp;rsquo; office, storyboarding ideas and talking through site features. A lot of time was spent on the list template, which is used extensively throughout the website. WebDevStudios did an amazing job hooking into a maps API to bring these pages to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zignal Labs</title>
      <link>https://tomrose.dev/projects/zignal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomrose.dev/projects/zignal/</guid>
      <description>Zignal Labs is a media analytics platform based in San Francisco. I worked with their in-house design and marketing teams to build out a custom, responsive WordPress theme. It includes product pages, a sortable resource library, a contact page with Google Map integration and lots of zigzags.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>